Stark, Arthur Additional Arbitration Cases 6048
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arthur Stark Additional Arbitration Cases
1994-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Stark, Arthur
6048
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records.
5771348
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Collective bargaining -- Postal service; Arbitration, Industrial; Stark, Arthur; National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.) --Archives
5771348
- USPS Exhibits Volumes 1-5. (Box 1)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume III- Stark DC (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume III- Stark DC (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume III- Stark DC (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume IV- Stark (Folder 1 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume IV- Stark (Folder 2 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume IV- Stark (Folder 3 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume IV- Stark (Folder 4 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume V- Stark-DC (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume V- Stark-DC & Agreement between Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO and U.S. Postal Service (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NALC opening brief; USPS Pre-hearing brief; NALC Contract proposals; CBA of NALC; CBA of APWU; Award & opinion - 8/19/95; "Postal Record" 9/95. (Box 2)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume I (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume II (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume II (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume VI (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Exhibits Volume VI (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NALC Contract Proposals 1995 Interest Arbitration (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1995 NALC-USPS Interest Arbitration NALC Mini Briefs (Box 2, Folder 7)
- NALC Exhibits Volumes 1-6. (Box 3)
  - Interest Arbitration The United States Postal Service (USPS) and The National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC) Volume XV, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume XVI, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume XIV Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume XIII, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume XII- Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume XI Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume X Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume IX Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume VIII, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume VII, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume VI Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume V, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume XIV, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume III Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume II Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume I Stark, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Transcripts USPS/NALC Volumes 1-18. (Box 4)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume XIV, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Interest Arbitration USPS and NALC Volume XIV Stark, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL- CIO Vol. I (Folder 1 of 2), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL- CIO Vol. I (Folder 2 of 2), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service Exhibits in Conn W/the Interest Arbitration W/the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO Vol. III (Folder 1 of 3), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL- CIO Vol. I (Folder 2 of 3), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL- CIO Vol. III (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service Exhibits in Conn W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO Vol. IV (Folder 1 of 3), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL- CIO Vol. IV (Folder 2 of 3), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL- CIO Vol. IV (Folder 3 of 3), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Postal Record Arbitration Cases between United Postal Service and Nat. Association of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn. W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO Vol. II (Folder 1 of 3), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn. W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO Vol. II (Folder 2 of 3), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn. W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO Vol. II (Folder 3 of 3), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn. W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO Vol. V (Folder 1 of 2), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn. W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO Vol. II (Folder 2 of 2), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- U.S. Postal Service Exhibits in Conn. W/ Interest Arbitration W/ the Nat. Assoc. of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO Vol. II (Folder 2 of 2), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)